HELLO, MY NAME IS

A Hao Wei Chen

and I'm a UX Designer

East Meadow, NY 11554

hwchen424@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/hwchen424 ==

behance.net/hwchen424

+1 (415) 549-6268

R

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

UX Designer with a background in Psychology. Experienced in communicating with different kinds of clients and customers. Proficient in working on their own to identify problems, researching solutions and communicating important findings with other team members.

WORK EXPERIENCE

From January 2018 to March 2020

COMMUNITY ASSISTANT SHARE, University of SF

San Francisco, California

- Managed front desk operations during peak hours and night shifts as a student employee.
- Acknowledged and welcomed residents, informed incoming guests, and resolved customer complaints and queries.
- Chosen as Community Assistant of the Month on multiple occasions by building residents.

O From December 2016 to January 2020

SALES ASSOCIATE Kissako Tea

San Francisco, California

- Promoted Japanese products and goods during business hours and major cultural events.
- Trained and supervised 2-3 seasonal hires during holiday seasons.
- Demonstrated exceptional customer service by building lasting relationships with regulars and newcomers alike.
- Trained by artisan tea makers from Ippodo Kyoto in making 4 different types of teas.

O From September 2018 to December 2018

PSYCHOLOGY INTERN Children's After School Arts

San Francisco, California

- Worked in a classroom setting with approximately 20-30 clients each week on mental well-being and emotional growth.
- Facilitated conflict resolution with clients and provided guidance to develop strong coping skills and behaviours when stressed.
- Lead discussions on important issues such as social justice, sexuality and discrimination to facilitate social awareness among young minds.

EDUCATION

O From March 2021 to April 2022

CERTIFICATE IN UX DESIGN

CareerFoundry

- Relevant Courses: UX Research, UI Design, Front-end Development
- O From August 2016 to May 2020

BACHELOR OF ARTS IN PSYCHOLOGY MINOR IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

The University of San Francisco

 Relevant Courses: Cognitive Psychology, UX Design, Advance Research Methods

PROJECTS

From March 2022 to April 2022

PORTFOLIO WEBSITE

Front-end Developement Capstone Project

- Applied UX and 508 compliance guidelines to design a responsive website for displaying personal and professional projects
- Coded the entirety of the website using HTML, CSS and Javascript.
- O From May 2021 to March 2022

EXPERT WEBAPP

UX/UI Design Course Capstone Project

- Applied a user-centred design process and mobile-first approach to design a responsive web app for connecting with experts.
- Carried out user research, data analysis, ideation, wire-framing, and creation of deliverables such as personas, and site maps.
- Designed 50+ high-fidelity screens, prototypes, and style guides based on stakeholder requests and end-user feedback.

₩

SKILLS

- Competitor Analysis
- User Interviews
- User Flows

- Design Systems
- Prototyping
- 508 Compliance

ह्य

TOOLS

- Figma
- Adobe XD, Photoshop
- Balsamia

- Design Systems
- Prototyping
- 508 Compliance